All right. Let's take a look at a sample solution for this exercise.
好吧好吧 让我们来看看这个练习的样本解决方案
ABC company hosted applications.
ABC 公司托管应用程序
ABC company shall provide general platform uptime of 99.9 percent.
ABC 公司应提供 99.9% 的通用平台正常运行时间
This will exclude regular maintenance window from 01:00 AM-05:00 AM,
这将排除 0 1:00 AM-05:00 AM 的常规维护窗口
Central Standard Time every Sunday,
每个星期天的中央标准时间
as well as windows from 01:00 AM-05:00 AM on
以及来自 01:00 AM-05:00 AM 的窗口
other days provided that ABC provides 24 hours of notice.
其他日子 规定 ABC 提供 24 小时的通知
Our second component to our SLA is that it's covering a third-party components.
我们 SLA 的第二个组成部分是它覆盖了第三方组件
Some components of our system are beyond our control,
我们系统的某些组件超出了我们的控制范围
and thus we can only pass through the provided SLA of these vendors.
因此 我们只能通过提供的这些供应商的 SLA
We only work with vendors and provide an SLA of
我们只与供应商合作并提供 SLA
99.9 percent or better for all critical services.
所有关键服务的 99.9% 或更高
The final component of our SLA covers non-critical components.
我们 SLA 的最终组件涵盖非关键组件
Those components deemed non-critical,
这些组件被视为非关键组件
listed below are subject to a 95 percent uptime SLA.
下面列出的是 95% 的 uptime SLA
These components are not core to our offering
这些组件不是我们产品的核心
but provides certain "nice to have" functionality.
但提供了一些 " 不错 " 的功能
In cases where these services are not available,
在这些服务不可用的情况下
our platform shall continue to operate and provide core functionality as normal.
我们的平台将继续运作 并提供正常的核心功能